Seungone Kim

□ louisdebroglie@kaist.ac.kr • ♦ https://github.com/SeungoneKim

My main research goal is to build neural models with enhanced reasoning capabilities and to supplement insufficient knowledge. Specifically, I am interested in injecting and utilizing commonsense knowledge to/with neural models [C2], analyzing to which extent neural models can do commonsense reasoning [P1], and enabling neural models to follow the given instructions [To Be Added].

Education

Yonsei University

Seoul, Korea

B.S. in Computer Science

March 2018 - February 2023

Early Graduation (7 semesters)

Advisor: Jinyoung Yeo

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Seoul, Korea March 2023 -

M.S. in Artificial Intelligence

Advisor : Minjoon Seo

Publications

Peer-Reviewed Conference Papers.....

- [C1] SG-MLP: Switch Gated Multi-Layer Perceptron Model for Natural Language Understanding
 Annual Conference of Korea Information Processing Society, 2021 (ACK 2021)
 Guijin Son, Seungone Kim, Se June Joo, Woojin Cho, JeongEun Nah
 [Paper] [Code]
- [C2] Mind the Gap! Injecting Commonsense Knowledge for Abstractive Dialogue Summarization
 Proceedings of the 29th International Conference on Computational Linguistics (COLING 2022)
 Seungone Kim*, Se June Joo*, Hyungjoo Chae*, Chaehyeong Kim*, Seungwon Hwang, Jinyoung Yeo [Paper] [Code]

Preprints....

• [P1] Can Language Models perform Abductive Commonsense Reasoning?

Seungone Kim

[Paper] [Code]

Research Experience

Yonsei University

Seoul, Korea

Internship at Soft Computing Laboratory

Apr 2021 - Aug 2021

I have participated in 'Industry - University Assignments' between Yonsei University and Samsung Electronics Research. I have built a neural model that transforms documents into tabular data. I built the overall pipeline along with a demo system to test it out.

Seoul National University

Seoul, Korea

Research Internship at Language and Data Intelligence Laboratory

Sep 2021 - Jun 2022

I have participated in a research project building a multilingual language model for low-resource languages via continual cross-lingual transfer during pre-training. Also, I have participated in the initial stage of building a Korean Language Model where I pre-trained a 11B sized decoder-only model with korean text corpus from scratch.

Yonsei University Seoul, Korea

Undergraduate Thesis advised by Conversational Intelligence Laboratory

Sep 2021 - Present

I have published my undergraduate thesis at COLING 2022 (long) as a first author [C2]. I proposed a method that injects commonsense knowledge inferences to solve abstractive dialogue summarization.

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

Seoul, Korea

Research Internship at Language and Knowledge Laboratory

Jul 2022 - Jan 2023

I participated in a research project building a distributed expert language model that tackles the weakness of Instruction-tuned LMs such as T0 and FLAN [O2]. This project is currently submitted to ICML 2023.

Technical and Personal skills

- Programming Languages: Python(Proficient), C++, C, Java
- Frameworks / Software Skills: PyTorch(Proficient), PyTorch Lightning(Proficient), Transformers(Proficient), FairSeq, Torch Geometric, NLTK, SpaCy
- O Software Skills: Linux, Google Cloud Platform, Docker, LATEX, Git, Wandb

Invited Talks

Commonsense Knowledge Consortium 1st Workshop

Hosted by II Chul Moon(KAIST), Chanyoung Park(KAIST), Jinyoung Yeo(Yonsei), Seungwon Hwang(SNU), Joseph Lim(KAIST), Jonghyeon Choi (Yonsei)

Presented about 'The Challenges in Commonsense Reasoning'

Yonsei University AI Workshop

Hosted by Jonghyeon Choi (Yonsei)

Presented my paper accepted at COLING 2022[C2]

Services

O Conference Reviewer: EACL 2023

Honors and Awards

2018 Yonsei - Nexon RC Creative Platform Competition

Yonsei University

Won 5th place

December 2018

Built an Internet Website that introduces about Korea to foreign transfer students. I've used ReactJS, NodeJS and SQLite.

Certificate of Achievement

US Department of the Army

Awarded as Sergeant

August 2020

I have served as a KATUSA (Korean Army Augmented to United States Army) in January 2019 - August 2020. I worked at a office consisted of Chief Warrant Officers who would fly helicopters to move Generals across the peninsula.

Voice AI Challenge

Seoul National University Hospital

Made to the Finals (Top 10 teams)

October 2021

I fine-tuned a transformer based model with voice/audio data to detect the type of disease to assist doctors.

Excellence Award at Annual Conference of KIPS, 2021

Korea Information Processing Society

Marked as Top 8 papers

November 2021

Awarded with my paper at ACK 2021[C1].

Grand Prize in Graduation Capstone

Yonsei University

Marked as Top 3 projects

July 2022

Awarded with my paper at COLING 2022[C2].

Yonsei Al Workshop NLP Best Paper Award

Received Award as the only Undergraduate Student

Samsung Electronics Research, Yonsei University

October 2022

Awarded with my paper at COLING 2022[C2].

Semester Academic Excellence Scholarship

Yonsei University

Fall 2020, Spring 2021, Fall 2021, Spring 2022

High / Highest Academic Honors

Yonsei University

Fall 2020, Spring 2021, Spring 2022